<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<quotes>
    <quote>"The all-important and crowning blessings of membership in the Church are those blessings which we receive in the temples of God."\r\n~ Thomas S. Monson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The supreme benefits of membership in the Church can only be realized through the exalting ordinances of the temple."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"I invite the Latter-day Saints to look to the temple of the Lord as the great symbol of your membership."\r\n~ Howard W. Hunter ~</quote>
    <quote>"The way you feel in the temple is a pattern for how you want to feel in your life."\r\n~ Neil L. Anderson ~</quote>
    <quote>"In the temple, all are dressed in spotless white. The symbolic purity of white likewise reminds us that God is to have a pure people."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Preparing children to enter the temple and participate in sacred ordinances is a vital part of the Lord's work of salvation."\r\n~ Thomas S. Monson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The temple sealing has greater meaning as life unfolds. It will help you draw ever closer together and find greater joy and fulfillment."\r\n~ Richard G. Scott ~</quote>
    <quote>"Every temple is a house of God, filling the same functions and with identical blessings and ordinances."\r\n~ Thomas S. Monson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Death cannot sever families sealed in the temple. They understand death as a necessary part of God's great plan of happiness."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Another comforting blessing of temple worship is the assurance of protection and peace from the storm that is upon us in our day."\r\n~ Ronald A. Rasband ~</quote>
    <quote>"Our temples are living, working testimonies to our faith in the reality of the resurrection."\r\n~ Dallin H. Oaks ~</quote>
    <quote>"To qualify one's self to go to the temple is a lofty ambition, a worthy achievement. We need to remind ourselves of its eternal purposes"\r\n~ Marvin J. Ashton ~</quote>
    <quote>"To hold a temple recommend is a priceless privilege and a tangible sign of obedience to God and His prophets."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Truly, the Lord desires that His people be a temple-motivated people."\r\n~ Howard W. Hunter ~</quote>
    <quote>"Honors bestowed upon me by men could not approach the inner peace provided by sealings performed in the house of the Lord."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"When you come to the temple you will love your family with a deeper love than you have ever felt before. The temple is about families."\r\n~ Richard H. Winkel ~</quote>
    <quote>"Never allow the goal of the temple to be out of your sight. Walk into His presence in purity and virtue, and receive His blessings"\r\n~ Elaine S. Dalton ~</quote>
    <quote>"You are never lost when you can see the temple. The temple will provide direction for you and your family in a world filled with chaos."\r\n~ Gary E. Stevenson ~</quote>
    <quote>"With increased attendance in the temples of our God, you shall receive increased personal revelation to bless your life..."\r\n~ Ezra Taft Benson ~</quote>
    <quote>"At the temple the dust of distraction seems to settle out, the fog and the haze seem to lift..."\r\n~ Boyd K. Packer ~</quote>
    <quote>"For behold, I have accepted this house, and my name shall be here; and I will manifest myself to my people in mercy in this house."\r\n~ Jesus Christ ~</quote>
    <quote>"As we come unto Christ and journey to higher ground, we will desire to spend more time in His temples..."\r\n~ Joseph B. Wirthlin ~</quote>
    <quote>"Some of the safest places that Heavenly Father has established for the gathering of His people are in the temples of the Lord. "\r\n~ Ronald A. Rasband ~</quote>
    <quote>"I make you a promise that if you will go to the house of the Lord, you will be blessed; life will be better for you."\r\n~ Gordon B. Hinckley ~</quote>
    <quote>"The temple is the house of the Lord. The basis for every temple ordinance and covenant is the Atonement of Jesus Christ."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The temple is a point of intersection between heaven and earth. The temple reminds us of all that is good and beautiful in the world."\r\n~ David A. Bednar ~</quote>
    <quote>"Everything that occurs in the temple is uplifting and ennobling. It speaks of the importance of the family and the eternity of the marriage relationship."\r\n~ Gordon B. Hinckley ~</quote>
    <quote>"I personally regard all of the houses of the Lord as the work of Jehovah, initiated by him, built by him, designed by him, and dedicated to him."\r\n~ Spencer W. Kimball ~</quote>
    <quote>"Let us be a temple-attending and a temple-loving people. Let us hasten to the temple as frequently as time and means and personal circumstances allow."\r\n~ Howard W. Hunter ~</quote>
    <quote>"A temple is literally the house of the Lord, reserved for ordinances of eternal significance."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Temples answer those soul-searching questions of the purpose of life, of why we are here and where we are going."\r\n~ Thomas S. Monson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The temple is a place of protection and a place of light and truth. It has the power of renewal, of strengthening, of refuge from the storm..."\r\n~ Dieter F. Uchtdorf ~</quote>
    <quote>"[The Temple] is a place where you can take the steps that lead to eternal life and a return home again to our Heavenly Father."\r\n~ Henry B. Eyring ~</quote>
    <quote>"One of the bellwether marks of the growth and vitality of the Church is the construction of temples."\r\n~ Gordon B. Hinckley ~</quote>
    <quote>"Each holy temple stands as a sign of our faith in life after death, and as a sacred step toward eternal glory for us and our families."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The Church is not fully organized, in its proper order, and cannot be, until the Temple is completed."\r\n~ Joseph Smith Jr. ~</quote>
    <quote>"Let this house be built unto my name, that I may reveal mine ordinances therein unto my people."\r\n~ Jesus Christ ~</quote>
    <quote>"Where there are temples, with the spirit of revelation resting upon those who administer therein, there the Lord's people will be found"\r\n~ Bruce R. McConkie ~</quote>
    <quote>"Temples are sacred for the closest communion between the Lord and those receiving the highest and most sacred ordinances of the holy priesthood."\r\n~ Howard W. Hunter ~</quote>
    <quote>"Temple marriage is more than just a place where the ceremony occurs; it is a whole orientation to life and marriage and home."\r\n~ Harold B. Lee ~</quote>
    <quote>"When we dedicate a house to the Lord, what we really do is dedicate ourselves to the Lord's service."\r\n~ Joseph Fielding Smith ~</quote>
    <quote>"I pray with all my soul that all members of the Church and their children ... may realize the great truths presented in the house of the Lord."\r\n~ David O. McKay ~</quote>
    <quote>"Marriage in the temple is one of the most beautiful things in all the world. A couple is led there by love, the most divine attribute of the human soul."\r\n~ David O. McKay ~</quote>
    <quote>"I pray that each of us will honor the Savior and make any necessary changes to see ourselves in His sacred temples."\r\n~ Quentin L. Cook ~</quote>
    <quote>"Every Temple completed ..., lessens the power of Satan on the earth, and increases the power of God and Godlines"\r\n~ George Q. Cannon ~</quote>
    <quote>"Certainly in a day and time like we live in, the importance of every temple built and dedicated to the Lord cannot be overstated."\r\n~ Ronald A. Rasband ~</quote>
    <quote>"I encourage our Saints all over the world, wherever possible, to strive to stand more often in holy places. Our most holy places are our sacred temples."\r\n~ James E. Faust ~</quote>
    <quote>"Come to the temple and place your burdens before the Lord and you'll be filled with a new spirit and confidence in the future."\r\n~ Thomas S. Monson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Whenever any kind of upheaval occurs in your life, the safest place to be spiritually is living inside your temple covenants!"\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"And daily in the temple, and in every house, they ceased not to teach and preach Jesus Christ."\r\n~ Acts 5:42 ~</quote>
    <quote>"And ye are to be taught from on high. Sanctify yourselves and ye shall be endowed with power, that ye may give even as I have spoken."\r\n~ Jesus Christ ~</quote>
    <quote>"And early in the morning [Jesus] came again into the temple, and all the people came unto him; and he sat down, and taught them."\r\n~ John 8:2 ~</quote>
    <quote>"The temple endowment was given by revelation. Thus, it is best understood by revelation, prayerfully sought with a sincere heart."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Finally it may be said that the temple endowment is not secret. All who meet the requirements for entrance to the temple may enjoy it."\r\n~ John A. Widtsoe ~</quote>
    <quote>"Each holy temple stands as a symbol of our membership in the Church, ... and as a sacred step toward eternal glory for us and our families."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Just as the Salt Lake Temple took 40 years to build, stone by stone, you are building a virtuous life, step by step."\r\n~ Mary N. Cook ~</quote>
    <quote>"If you don't yet love to attend the temple, go more often - not less. Let the Lord, through His Spirit, teach and inspire you there."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"There, in the house of the Lord, you can learn what you need to know to be truly free. ... the chance to be totally unselfish - a rarity in today's world."\r\n~ Robert L. Simpson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Thus Israel gathers for the purpose of building temples in which the ordinances of salvation and exaltation are performed for the living and the dead."\r\n~ Bruce R. McConkie ~</quote>
    <quote><![CDATA["...establish a house, even a house of prayer, a house of fasting, a house of faith, a house of learning, a house of glory, a house of order, a house of God."\r\n~ D & C  88:119 ~]]></quote>
    <quote>"I have hallowed this house, which thou hast built, to put my name there for ever; and mine eyes and mine heart shall be there perpetually."\r\n~ I Kings 9:3 ~</quote>
    <quote>"I plead with you to seek - prayerfully and consistently - to understand temple covenants and ordinances."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"And I, Nephi, did build a temple; and I did construct it after the manner of the temple of Solomon...and the workmanship thereof was exceedingly fine."\r\n~ 2 Nephi 5:16 ~</quote>
    <quote>"Regular temple attendance is one of the simplest ways you can bless those who are waiting in the spirit world."\r\n~ David B. Haight ~</quote>
    <quote>"As you are true to your covenants made in the temple, you will be strengthened by His power."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"I personally regard all of the houses of the Lord as the work of Jehovah, initiated by him, built by him, designed by him, and dedicated to him."\r\n~ Spencer W. Kimball ~</quote>
    <quote>"Temple. One other word is equal in importance... Home. Put the words holy temple and home together, and you have described the house of the Lord!"\r\n~ Boyd K. Packer ~</quote>
    <quote>"We have thought of thy loving kindness, O God, in the midst of thy temple."\r\n~ Psalms 48:9 ~</quote>
    <quote>"The time will come when there will be temples established over every portion of the land, ... and work for our kindred dead night and day."\r\n~ Lorenzo Snow ~</quote>
    <quote>"I promise that increased time in the temple will bless your life in ways nothing else can."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The feelings of holiness in my home prepared me for feelings of holiness in the temple."\r\n~ James E. Faust ~</quote>
    <quote>"Everything we believe and every promise God has made to His covenant people come together in the temple."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The real blessings of the temple come as we ... feel a spirit of reverence for the temple and a spirit of worship."\r\n~ L. Lionel Kendrick ~</quote>
    <quote>"In every age, the temple has underscored the precious truth that those who make covenants with God and keep them are children of the covenant."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The Temple - the house of the Lord - is a place of security unlike any other."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Our eyes should gaze beyond the baptismal font to the holy temple. The great garner into which the sheaves should be gathered is the holy temple."\r\n~ Neal A. Maxwell ~</quote>
    <quote>"Each person who makes covenants in baptismal fonts and in temples - and keeps them - has increased access to the power of Jesus Christ."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Each of our temples is an expression of our testimony that life beyond the grave is as real and as certain as is our life here on earth."\r\n~ Thomas S. Monson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The ultimate objective of the gathering of Israel is to bring the blessings of the temple to God's faithful children."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Yea, and my presence shall be there, for I will come into it, and all the pure in heart that shall come into it shall see God."\r\n ~ Jesus Christ ~</quote>
    <quote>"Everything taught in the temple, through instruction and through the Spirit, increases our understanding of Jesus Christ."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"But let us...recite the crowning reason for gathering to Zion or to her stakes. It is to receive the blessings found in the temples of the Lord."\r\n~ Bruce R. McConkie ~</quote>
    <quote>"As we come unto Christ and journey to higher ground, we will desire to spend more time in His temples..."\r\n~ Joseph B. Wirthlin ~</quote>
    <quote>"The temple lies at the center of strengthening our faith and spiritual fortitude because the Savior and His doctrine are the very heart of the temple."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The temple is a place where we can find peace. There we receive a renewed dedication to the gospel and a strengthened resolve to keep the commandments."\r\n~ Thomas S. Monson ~</quote>
    <quote>"When you bring your temple recommend, a contrite heart, and a seeking mind to the Lord's house of learning, He will teach you."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Understanding the eternal nature of the temple will draw you to your family; understanding the eternal nature of the family will draw you to the temple."\r\n~ Gary E. Stevenson ~</quote>
    <quote>"As we build and maintain these temples, we pray that each of you will build and maintain yourself so you can be worthy to enter the holy temple."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"All of the ordinances that take place in the house of the Lord are expressions of our belief in the immortality of the human soul."\r\n~ Gordon B. Hinckley ~</quote>
    <quote>"When you come to the temple you will love your family with a deeper love than you have ever felt before. The temple is about families."\r\n~ Richard H. Winkel ~</quote>
    <quote>"But the Lord is in his holy temple: let all the earth keep silence before him."\r\n~ Habakkuk 2:20 ~</quote>
    <quote>"With the dedication of each new temple, additional godly power comes into the world to strengthen us and counteracts the intensifying efforts of the adversary."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The temple is ... the most sacred and holy place on earth and should be treated with the greatest degree of reverence and respect."\r\n~ L. Lionel Kendrick ~</quote>
    <quote>"More regular time in the temple will allow the Lord to teach you how to draw upon His priesthood power with which you have been endowed in His temple."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"We must build more temples, and we must build them more quickly. This is the season to build temples. They are needed, and we have the means to do so."\r\n~ Gordon B. Hinckley ~</quote>
    <quote>"During times of our distress when temples are closed, you can still draw upon the power of your temple covenants and endowment as you honor your covenants."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"To accomplish this work there will have to be not only one temple but thousands of them..."\r\n~ Brigham Young ~</quote>
    <quote>"There are many different ways to see the face of Christ, and there is no better place than in His holy house."\r\n~ Neil L. Andersen ~</quote>
    <quote>"Frequent participation in the ordinances of the temple can create a pattern of devotion to the Lord. When you keep your temple covenants and remember them, you invite the companionship of the Holy Ghost to both strengthen and purify you."\r\n~ Henry B. Eyring ~</quote>
    <quote>"Building and maintaining temples may not change your life, but spending your time in the temple surely will."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The peace of the temple is a soothing balm to the wounded soul. ... The temple projects our brief moment in mortality onto the wide screen of eternity."\r\n~ Neil L. Anderson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The crowning jewel of the Restoration is the holy temple. Its sacred ordinances and covenants are pivotal to preparing a people who are ready to welcome the Savior at His Second Coming."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>    
    <quote>"Spending more time in the temple builds faith. And your service and worship in the temple will help you to think celestial."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The temple is a place of revelation...There you are drawn closer to the Savior and given greater access to His power. There you are guided in solving the problems in your life, even your most perplexing problems."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"The ordinances and covenants of the temple are of eternal significance. We continue to build more temples to make these sacred possibilities become a reality in each of your lives."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"In His house, we are literally endowed with heavenly power. Our faith in Jesus Christ and our love for Him are confirmed and fortified. We are spiritually assured of our true identity and the purposes of life."\r\n~ Neil L. Andersen ~</quote>
    <quote>"The Lord is directing us to build these temples to help us think celestial."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"As temples come closer to us in many places, a temple sacrifice we can offer is to seek holiness in the house of the Lord more frequently."\r\n~ Gerrit W. Gong ~</quote>
    <quote>"When we walk out of the temple, transformed by our hope in the promises of the covenants, armed with power from on high, we take the temple with us into our homes and lives."\r\n~ Ulisses Soares ~</quote>
    <quote>"As we come with willing hearts to the house of the Lord, the most holy place on earth, we grow up in the Lord and can 'receive a fulness of the Holy Ghost.'"\r\n~ Neil L. Andersen ~</quote>
    <quote>"The temple is the gateway to the greatest blessings God has in store for each of us, for the temple is the only place on earth where we may receive all of the blessings promised to Abraham."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Being temple bound secures us to the Savior, giving us proper direction and stability while ensuring we have covenant confidence through Jesus Christ."\r\n~ Ulisses Soares ~</quote>
    <quote>"Nothing will help you more to hold fast to the iron rod than worshipping in the temple as regularly as your circumstances permit...Nothing will open the heavens more. Nothing!"\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"As we make covenants in holiness before God and commit to follow the Savior, we receive the power to change our hearts, renew our spirits, and deepen our relationship with Him."\r\n~ Ulisses Soares ~</quote>
    <quote>"In His holy house, if we will, we can be still and know that God is our Heavenly Father, we are His children, and Jesus Christ is our Savior."\r\n~ David A. Bednar ~</quote>
    <quote>"We are promised that 'no combination of wickedness' will prevail over those who worship in the house of the Lord."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"If we change our preparation to enter the temple, we will change our experience in the temple, which will transform our lives outside of the temple."\r\n~ Ulisses Soares ~</quote>
    <quote>"The ordinances and associated covenants of the temple are requirements for exaltation in the celestial kingdom, which is eternal life, 'the greatest of all the gifts of God.'"\r\n~ Dallin H. Oaks ~</quote>
    <quote>"We are instructed that all who worship in the temple will have the power of God and angels having 'charge over them.'"\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"When we enter the Lord's house, we embark on a sacred journey of learning to become higher and holier disciples of Christ."\r\n~ Ulisses Soares ~</quote>
    <quote>"We are also promised that in the temple we may 'receive a fulness of the Holy Ghost.' Imagine what that promise means in terms of having the heavens open for each earnest seeker of eternal truth."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Regularly performing ordinances for our ancestors in the temple brings a sweet and sure confirmation that life continues beyond the veil."\r\n~ Neil L. Andersen ~</quote>
    <quote>"The house of the Lord is where we can be transformed in higher and holier ways...I assure you that having the spirit of the Lord's house in us changes us, completely."\r\n~ Ulisses Soares ~</quote>
    <quote>"Regular temple worship will enhance the way you see yourself and how you fit into God's magnificent plan. I promise you that."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"I humbly testify that as we attend the temple, we can be reminded of the eternal nature of our spirits, our relationship with the Father and His divine Son, and our ultimate desire to return to our heavenly home."\r\n~ Henry B. Eyring ~</quote>
    <quote>"Time in the temple will help you to think celestial and to catch a vision of who you really are, who you can become, and the kind of life you can have forever."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"No matter the outcome, all will be well because of temple covenants."\r\n~ Henry B. Eyring ~</quote>
    <quote>"Here is my promise to you: Every sincere seeker of Jesus Christ will find Him in the temple. You will feel His mercy. You will find answers to your most vexing questions. You will better comprehend the joy of His gospel."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Most of our experiences in the house of the Lord bring joyful peace and quiet revelation more than dramatic intervention. But be assured: angels do have charge over us!"\r\n~ Neil L. Andersen ~</quote>
    <quote>"If you don’t yet love to attend the temple, go more often—not less. Let the Lord, through His Spirit, teach and inspire you there."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"If you don’t yet love to attend the temple, go more often—not less. ... I promise you that over time, the temple will become a place of safety, solace, and revelation."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Those who gain genuine confidence in the covenants made in the house of the Lord through Jesus Christ possess one of the most powerful forces that we can access in this life."\r\n~ Ulisses Soares ~</quote>
    <quote>"In the temple, we receive protection from the buffetings of the world. We experience the pure love of Jesus Christ and our Heavenly Father in great abundance!"\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"I humbly testify that as we attend the temple, we can be reminded of the eternal nature of our spirits, our relationship with the Father and His divine Son, and our ultimate desire to return to our heavenly home."\r\n~ Henry B. Eyring ~</quote>
    <quote>"The blessings of the temple help to gather Israel on both sides of the veil. These blessings also help to prepare a people who will help prepare the world for the Second Coming of the Lord!"\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Of course, holiness to the Lord in everyday life includes coming more often to the Lord in His holy house."\r\n~ Gerrit W. Gong ~</quote>
    <quote>"Regular worship in the house of the Lord increases our capacity for both virtue and charity. Thus, time in the temple increases our confidence before the Lord."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
    <quote>"Frequent participation in the ordinances of the temple can create a pattern of devotion to the Lord."\r\n~ Henry B. Eyring ~</quote>
    <quote>"Increased time in the temple will help us prepare for the Second Coming of our Savior, Jesus Christ."\r\n~ Russell M. Nelson ~</quote>
</quotes>
